ubid.com 2007-12-08

# uBid.com - Help Pages

| 

Browse Help

uBid Info

|   
---  
  
| 

** What is uBid.com's Privacy & Security Policy? **

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.ubid.com&sealid=101)(Last Updated: July 6, 2005)

uBid.com, Inc. ("uBid.com") has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. As this policy may change from time to time, please check back periodically.

uBid.com uses the information we collect about you to process orders. When you register at uBid.com, we collect your name, email addresses, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date in order to process and fulfill your order. In some instances, products ordered at uBid.com are shipped directly from our vendors, and some of your information is shared with these vendors to enable them to fulfill and ship your order.

When you sign up for uBid.com Auction Alerts, we need only an email address to send you the email topics that you have selected. We also use your email address to send you email notice of your bid and order status, and we may use your email address to send you notice of upgrades or changes to uBid.com, new services, and special offers. You may choose not to receive any of these emails when you register, or at a later date, by accessing uBid.com Auction Alerts.

We occasionally will ask for additional information from you. For instance, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address in connection with a contest or other promotional feature in which you participate, so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We may offer contests or promotions with third parties; policies concerning use of your personal data gathered in connection with any such contest or promotion will be specifically set forth in the rules and policies applicable to the contest or promotion.

uBid.com offers a service called "Tell a Buddy" that allows you to notify friends about open auctions. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not save or share your buddies email address, they are only used for this one time mailing. Please note, however, that uBid.com opposes the practice of sending unsolicited commercial emails, also known as "spam". Therefore, we request that you send "Tell a Buddy" emails only to people known by you who may be interested in the auction. If someone asks you not to send these emails to him or her, please comply. 

When you bid on an item, you must enter the amount of your bid, your uBid.com Login ID and your password. Only your initials, city and state and your bid will be publicly available in the Current Winning Bids history.

Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all applicable local laws and rules regarding online conduct and privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of technical and personal data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are pieces of information that are passed to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. uBid.com uses cookies to recognize repeat visitors, to automatically enter your login ID in our bid form, and to provide additional features to make bidding & buying at uBid.com easier and more efficient. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can turn them off using your browser's settings **.** We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. ****

**Sharing data with third parties**  
Upon registration with uBid.com, each of our customers is assigned a random and anonymous customer number, which we use to track customer orders. This customer number is different from any custom login ID selected by you and may be passed to third party vendors with whom we work to provide more efficient and relevant services to our users. Our anonymous customer numbers may be used to measure traffic and visiting patterns on uBid.com and on other websites on the Internet. We may also compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregated basis, and may share such aggregated data with selected third parties. uBid.com can (and you authorize us to) release any information about you when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, enforce other uBid.com rights, or protect the rights, property or safety of uBid.com, the uBid.com Web site, our users, or others. Further, as permitted by applicable law, uBid.com can (and you authorize us to) disclose your login ID, name, street, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, company and any other information in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity whenever uBid.com in its sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate. In the event uBid.com, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

In addition, we may share information about you with third parties as necessary to complete a transaction requested by you or to enable them to provide special opportunities and offers to you. We may share information about you with our business partners, affiliates or other third parties with your approval only. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer want us to share information you provide with third parties, you may correct, update, or unsubscribe by making the change in My Account located in My Page on uBid.com, or by contacting our Customer Care department at 1-866-WIN-UBID.

You may choose whether or not to receive Outbid and order processing emails in My Account and in My Mailbox. By registering at uBid.com, you consent to the collection and use of this information by uBid.com for order processing, Auction Alert emails, or the sharing of your personally identifiable information to our business partners (with your consent only). In the event of changes in our privacy policy, this page will be updated with the current information.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by 24/7 Real Media, our Web advertising partner, and other third-party advertising companies. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information regarding your cookies, disabling your cookies, and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here [http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.a).

**What is the uBidShopper privacy policy?**  
At uBidShopper, it is our mission to provide an easy to use tool that makes online shopping easier, faster, safer and above all - fun. We're committed to your privacy and believe that it should be respected and protected. Our [Privacy Policy](http://www.smartshopper.com/SmartShopper/affiliates/uBid/PrivacyPolicy.aspx) is simple. We don't collect any personal information about you or your shopping habits. We use only the information you enter when you search for a product or service. (That's what we need to automatically compare and find the best web deals.) We will not trade, rent or sell that information with anyone else.

**Links**  
This Web site may contain links to other web sites. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other web sites is subject to the terms and conditions of those web sites, including the privacy policies of those web sites.

**Children's Privacy**  
This Web site is designed for an adult audience only, and children should not use this Web site. We will not intentionally collect online any personal information (such as a child's name or e-mail address) from children under the age of 13. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us and we will address the issue.

** Security**

**How your information is encrypted**  
There are certain areas on the site where you may enter and submit additional information. Certain of these areas are encrypted using SSL encrypted transmissions between your Web browser and our Web server. This is designed to reduce the chance that someone (e.g. on your network at work or at your Internet service provider) may try to compromise your private information as it travels from your Web browser to our secure server. You'll know when transmitted data is encrypted by a security notice when you enter an encrypted page, and by the presence of an icon on your browser, either a key for Netscape or a lock for Microsoft Internet Explorer. The pages where you submit your account information, place a bid, and receive confirmation of a successful bid are all encrypted. In addition, your credit card information is encrypted within the uBid.com database and access to such information is restricted. This system is unique and designed to provide you with additional security when purchasing items on uBid.com.

**Protecting your login ID and password**  
Always keep your uBid.com account number and password secret. They are your only identification for bidding purposes. If you receive information about a bid you did not place, or questionable communications regarding your account, please contact uBid.com Customer Support immediately by [email](http://www.ubid.net/help/topic38.asp) or by telephone at 1-866-WIN-UBID. One potential way for someone to steal your login ID and password is if you bookmark any area on MyPage or a bid submission page. This is a concern if your browser is available to other people at work, home, or especially if you use a browser at a public internet cafe. You should not bookmark such pages and you should clear the browser cache and quit the browser completely when you are done surfing uBid.com. We have also worked to protect you against such a mistake. Even if someone obtains both your login ID and password, the system is designed to restrict access to your credit card information because that field is cleared when they log in to My Page.

**About SSL, security, and firewall problems**  
Some older browsers (such as IE 3.0.2) have known SSL bugs. These can result in the browser crashing on SSL pages or giving error messages. We recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of whatever browser you prefer. For AOL users, you may be able to upgrade your security by downloading and replacing the schannel.dll from Microsoft. For users behind corporate firewalls, you need to configure your web browser security settings. This includes setting https or secure proxy settings. To determine if you have such a security problem, you can edit a secure URL, replacing 'https' (secure) with 'http' (insecure). If the page works with http:// but not https://, then you have a problem with your security settings. You should contact your system administrator for assistance.

**Technical Details About Encryption**  
uBid.com operates with a VeriSign Digital Server Certificate, featuring cryptographic techniques to reduce the risk that Digital IDs are not forged or tampered with. These techniques, developed by RSA Data Security, use a matched pair of encryption and decryption keys. This use of matched-key cryptography with a 1024-bit key length provides a level of security unavailable with conventional secret key cryptography.

**TRUSTe**  
uBid.com, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site [ www.ubid.com](http://www.ubid.com/). Because this Website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact uBid.com at 773-272-5000. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [ http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

uBid.com, Inc. -- 8725 West Higgins Rd., 9th Floor - Chicago, IL 60631 - 773-272-5000
